<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic id="topic_n4x_2z3_pdb">
    <title>Version 1.5.6</title>
    <abstract>Released Date: March 30, 2017</abstract>
    <prolog>
        <critdates>
            <!--Carol-->
            <revised modified="2018/06/20"/>
        </critdates>
    </prolog>
    <body>
        <section id="section_p3t_2bx_pdb">
            <title>Optimization</title>
            <p><image href="../Images/horizon.png" id="image_q3t_2bx_pdb"/></p>
            <p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Changed all the default system music on hold files to the Asterisk version
                        13 music on hold files. The music on hold files are authorized to use.</li>
                    <li>Updated English, Chinese, Turkish, Spanish, and Hebrew system prompts.</li>
                    <li>Optimized CDR and Recordings feature: the system will record the un-answered
                        call if the queue agents didn’t answer the call. </li>
                    <li>Optimized CDR and Recordings feature: the PBX administrator can delete and
                        download call logs and recording files in batch.</li>
                    <li>Optimized CDR and Recordings feature: if an extension has a DOD number, the
                        call log will display the extension number and the DOD number.</li>
                    <li>Optimized CDR and Recordings feature: users can click a column heading to
                        sort the table in ascending or descending order.</li>
                    <li>Optimized CDR and Recordings feature: users can choose an extension to play
                        recording file on the web interface.</li>
                    <li>Optimized Voicemail feature: if voicemails have been played or deleted on
                        Web interface, the IP phone will synchronize the voicemail status.</li>
                    <li>Optimized Voicemail feature: users can change the voicemail system’s “Busy
                        Prompt” and “Unavailable Prompt” (Settings > PBX > General > Voicemail >
                        Greeting Options). </li>
                    <li>Optimized Voicemail feature: when users call in the PBX’s IVR, they can dial
                        *02 to check voicemails. To achieve this function, you need to enable “Dial
                        to Check Voicemail” on the IVR edit page.</li>
                    <li>Optimized User Permission: allow users to delete auto recording files;
                        separate reboot permission and reset permission.</li>
                    <li>Optimized DOD Settings: users can import and export DOD numbers.</li>
                    <li>Optimized SIP Caller ID feature: different SIP trunks can get Caller ID from
                        different SIP fields. There is a global “Get Caller ID From” setting on “PBX
                        > General > SIP > Advanced” page. You can set a different “Get Caller ID
                        From” for a specific SIP trunk on the trunk edit page.</li>
                    <li>Optimized SIP DID feature: added support for getting DID number from
                        “Diversion” and “P-Asserted-Identify” (PBX > General > SIP > Advanced).</li>
                    <li>Optimized SIP Outbound SIP Registrations Setting: the “Default
                        Incoming/Outgoing Registration Time” is set to 1800 seconds.</li>
                    <li>Optimized Call Transferring: “Send Diversion ID” (PBX > General > SIP >
                        Advanced) will work for extension “Call Forwarding” and transfer feature
                        codes (*03, *3). When an incoming call is forwarded or when using *03 or *3
                        to transfer a call, the original caller’s number will be displayed.</li>
                    <li>Optimized SLA feature: users can choose a failover destination for a SLA
                        trunk.</li>
                    <li>Optimized Event Center: added “Network Drive Lost Connection” notification
                        setting.</li>
                    <li>Optimized Static Route: users can choose adding static route to LAN gateway
                        or WAN gateway.</li>
                    <li>Optimized System Email Password Setting: the password setting is allowed to
                        enter any special characters.</li>
                    <li>Optimized Auto Cleanup settings: the default <ph id="OLE_LINK4">“Max Number
                            of CDR” on S20/S50/S100 is 200000</ph>, the default “Max Number of CDR”
                        on S300 is 50000. The default value of “CDR Preservation Duration”, “Files
                        Preservation Duration” and “Recordings Preservation Duration” are set to 0,
                        meaning no limit.</li>
                    <li>Optimized Auto Cleanup feature: when the CDR reaches over 90% of the “Max
                        number of CDR”, the system will send notification.</li>
                    <li>Optimized SIP feature: support requests of MESSAGE SIP packet (PBX > General
                        > SIP > Advanced).</li>
                    <li>Optimized DID Settings: support DID numbers that start with digit 0 and
                        support DID numbers that contain character “+”.</li>
                    <li>Optimized FXO Settings: users can change the FXO trunk’s “DTMF Duration” and
                        “DTMF Gap” (PBX > General).</li>
                    <li>Optimized FXO Settings: users can manually release a FXO trunk on web
                        interface (FXO Trunk > Advanced > Other Settings).</li>
                    <li>Optimized FXO Hangup Detection feature: support hang up a call by “Loop
                        Current Disconnect” method. This method is used when connecting the S-Series
                        IPPBX to a traditional PBX, and the traditional PBX uses this method for
                        signaling call termination.</li>
                </ul>
            </p>
        </section>
        <section id="section_bsn_fbx_pdb">
            <title>Fixed Bug</title>
            <p><image href="../Images/horizon.png" id="image_csn_fbx_pdb"/></p>
            <p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fixed BLF LED status issue: the BLF LED would stay in Green status after
                        rebooting S-Series IPPBX.PBX.</li>
                    <li>Fixed Voicemail issue: the voicemails were not deleted automatically even
                        the option “Delete Voicemail” was enabled.</li>
                    <li>Fixed Emergency Call issue: when the PBX reached the max number of
                        concurrent calls, emergency calls could not work.</li>
                    <li>Fixed Time Condition issue: if time condition status was force changed by
                        feature code, distinctive ring tones on inbound routes could not work.</li>
                    <li>Fixed Time Condition issue: the IP phone BLF key could not correctly
                        indicate the time condition status.</li>
                    <li>Fixed the SMS issue: if an email contains Greek words, sending this email to
                        SMS, the SMS contents would appear garbled words; Sending SMS to email also
                        had this problem.</li>
                    <li>Fixed Email to SMS issue: if the email contains Polish words, sending email
                        to SMS would fail. </li>
                    <li>Fixed compatibility issue with some VOIP ISP: making outbound calls with the
                        VoIP trunk, the calls would be disconnected after 30 seconds.</li>
                    <li>Fixed DID number matching issue on inbound route: the system could not match
                        DID number correctly if there were multiple inbound routes configured with
                        the same Peer-to-Peer SIP trunk and different DID numbers.</li>
                    <li>Fixed Hot Standby issue: after enabling Hot Standby feature, the system’s
                        default gateway would automatically be changed to LAN gateway. </li>
                    <li>Fixed Hot Standby issue: configurations on the primary server and standby
                        server could not be synchronized.</li>
                    <li>Fixed Paging Group issue: if a user called the PBX’s FXO trunk, and the call
                        reached a paging group, all the group members hung up the call, but call was
                        still connected.</li>
                    <li>Fixed the Auto Defense issue: if an IP was listed in blacklist due to SSH
                        accessing failure, this IP would have no authority to access the PBX web
                        interface.</li>
                    <li>Fixed Voicemail issue: system would reserve the prompt “please leave a
                        message after the tone”, even users had custom “Busy prompt” and
                        “Unavailable prompt”. </li>
                    <li>Fixed the Voicemail issue: the S-Series IPPBX would not send RTP packets
                        when users were leaving voicemail messages, this would cause some ISP
                        consider the PBX is not alive and disconnect the call. </li>
                    <li>Fixed File Share issue: Win 10 users could not access the shared files;
                        Window users need to change the PC LAN Manager authentication level, or they
                        cannot access the shared files.</li>
                    <li>Fixed the File Share issue: if the user first enabled file share feature
                        then installed the external storage device, the file share feature would not
                        work. </li>
                    <li>Fixed the issue that if ring group member or queue agent’s extension was not
                        registered, the extension and the mobility extension could not ring
                        simultaneously. </li>
                    <li>Fixed the Outbound route issue: the system could not correctly match
                        outbound route if multiple outbound routes were configured with the same
                        dial pattern.</li>
                    <li>Fixed the User Permission issue: a user with permission to check and
                        download CDR and recordings could not check and download his/her own CDR and
                        recordings.</li>
                    <li>Fixed CDR and Recordings issue: pickup calls were not recorded in the call
                        log.</li>
                    <li>Fixed CDR and Recordings issue: if the research result includes tens of
                        thousands of records, downloading the research results would fail.</li>
                    <li>Fixed NAT issue: if NAT method was set to a domain, and when the domain
                        could not be resolved, the NAT page would be unreachable, debugging Asterisk
                        also would fail.</li>
                    <li>Fixed compatibility issue with some Analog phones: if a trunk had no Caller
                        ID service, when users call in the trunk, and the call reached an analog
                        phone, the phone might crash.</li>
                    <li>Fixed the issue that extension IP Restriction feature could not work
                        properly.</li>
                    <li>Fixed the IAX issues: IAX trunk’s domain name could not automatically
                        update; using IAX might cause memory leaks.</li>
                </ul>
            </p>
        </section>
    </body>
</topic>
