<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic id="topic_t52_l4k_jdb">
  <title>Version 30.5.0.30</title>
  <abstract>Released Date: September 22, 2017</abstract>
  <prolog>
    <critdates>
      <!--Carol-->
      <revised modified="2018/06/20"/>
    </critdates>
  </prolog>
  <body>
    <section id="section_gff_vsk_jdb">
      <title>Upgrade Notes:</title>
      <p>
        <ul id="ul_ujz_xsk_jdb">
          <li>This version has greatly enhanced the security mechanism; we strongly suggest all
            users upgrade to this new version.</li>
          <li>After upgrading to version 30.5.0.30, to make sure Linkus can be properly used, please
            upgrade Linkus App to 1.4.7 in App Center. </li>
          <li>If you are using Hot Standby, please disable it first, and upgrade the two PBXs
            separately before enabling Hot Standby again. Otherwise, the PBX's extensions will fail
            to register after the upgrade.</li>
        </ul>
      </p>
    </section>
    <section id="section_nyk_p4g_jdb">
      <title>New Feature</title>
      <p><image href="../Images/horizon.png" id="image_acs_lzv_pdb"/></p>
      <p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added API feature: Third-party applications can get IPPBX information via the API.
            This feature is supported in S50, S100, S300.</li>
        </ul>
      </p>
    </section>
    <section id="section_gzb_54g_jdb">
      <title>Optimization</title>
      <p><image href="../Images/horizon.png" id="image_y1c_nzv_pdb"/></p>
      <p>
        <ul id="ul_v2k_4tk_jdb">
          <li>Reduced background noise when playing system prompts and global recording in Linkus
            Mobile Clients.</li>
          <li>Optimized Web interface login security: after five unsuccessful login attempts in the
            Web interface, instead of locking the account for 10 minutes, the IP address will be
            added into the firewall blacklist.</li>
          <li>Optimized extension registration security: when failed to register extension using the
            same IP address for five times in five minutes, the IP address will be added into the
            firewall blacklist.</li>
        </ul>
      </p>
    </section>
    <section id="section_cmm_x4g_jdb">
      <title>Fixed Bug</title>
      <p><image href="../Images/horizon.png" id="image_m1b_4zv_pdb"/></p>
      <p>
        <ul id="ul_g4m_ptk_jdb">
          <li>Fixed Attended Transfer issue on Linkus Mobile Client: when Linkus Mobile Client user
            A (extension A) made an outbound call through the GSM trunk, and transferred it to the
            extension B during the call using the “Attended Transfer” feature, then user A pressed
            the “Transfer” button before extension B could press the “Answer”, the call would be
            hung up..</li>
          <li>Fixed the issue that DTMF on Polycom Phones did not take effect.</li>
          <li>Fixed the issue that when administrator sent emails containing a QR code for users to
            login their Linkus Mobile Client account, some emails would display garbage
            characters.</li>
        </ul>
      </p>
    </section>
  </body>
</topic>
